<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog | Yuto Lewis Terashima</title>
    <link>https://ylt-apcom.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ylt-apcom.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://ylt-apcom.io/media/icon_hu4009627630656268537.png</url>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://ylt-apcom.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Presentation Award for Collaborative Research Idea Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://ylt-apcom.io/post/jsces-summer-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ylt-apcom.io/post/jsces-summer-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Best Presentation Award&lt;/strong&gt; was granted for outstanding performance at the &lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Research Idea Hackathon&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The presented idea focused on integrating &lt;strong&gt;Finite Element Methods (FEM)&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Molecular Dynamics (MD)&lt;/strong&gt; simulations to explore the mechanical properties of advanced materials. This innovative approach emphasizes the importance of &lt;strong&gt;multi-scale simulations&lt;/strong&gt; in bridging fine-scale material behaviors and coarse-scale applications, contributing significantly to computational mechanics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hackathon provided a platform for researchers from various disciplines to collaborate, exchange ideas, and advance cutting-edge research methodologies, demonstrating the value of teamwork in driving scientific innovation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitou-Target Program for Quantum Computing Technology</title>
      <link>https://ylt-apcom.io/post/mitou-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ylt-apcom.io/post/mitou-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Mitou-Target Program&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;Quantum Computing Technology&lt;/strong&gt; selected this project in 2023 for its innovative approach to solving optimization problems using quantum algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project involves the development of a &lt;strong&gt;quantum annealing-based service&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;route optimization&lt;/strong&gt; in logistics, focusing on enhancing computational efficiency and scalability. By leveraging state-of-the-art quantum computing platforms, the project aims to address real-world challenges in the logistics and transportation sectors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This recognition underlines the project&amp;rsquo;s potential to drive technological advancements in the field of &lt;strong&gt;quantum optimization&lt;/strong&gt; and its applications to industrial problems, marking a significant milestone in the integration of quantum computing into everyday solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For further details, see the official &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ipa.go.jp/jinzai/mitou/target/2023/gaiyou_tr-2.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Mitou-Target Program Page&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://amplify.fixstars.com/en/customers/interview/mitou2023/cvrp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Fixstars Amplify Interview&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
